{
  "questions": [
      {
        "question": "3 + 5 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "8",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "7", "6", "9" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "10 + 2 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "12",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "6", "14", "7" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "4 + 6 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "10",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "20", "22", "25" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "15 + 3 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "18",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "4", "6", "3" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "8 + 9 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "17",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "16", "18", "15" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "20 + 7 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "27",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "14", "12", "15" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "9 + 3 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "12",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "24", "30", "25" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "18 + 2 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "20",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "8", "10", "6" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "6 + 7 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "13",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "12", "14", "11" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "30 + 15 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "45",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "14", "16", "20" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "5 + 5 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "10",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "20", "24", "30" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "27 + 3 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "30",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "8", "10", "6" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "12 + 6 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "18",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "17", "19", "16" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "45 + 20 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "65",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "24", "26", "30" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "8 + 4 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "12",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "30", "35", "28" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "36 + 4 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "40",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "8", "10", "6" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "9 + 8 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "17",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "16", "18", "15" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "25 + 12 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "37",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "14", "16", "20" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "6 + 9 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "15",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "50", "60", "48" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "63 + 7 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "70",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "8", "10", "6" ]
      }
  ]
}